<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="7.0.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">Using steroids in MLB is cheating, plain and simple.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Players who used steroids should be permanently banned from the Hall of Fame.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Steroid use undermines the integrity of the game.</statement>
     <statement id="4">If everyone has access to performance-enhancing drugs, it levels the playing field.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Steroid users should be allowed in the Hall of Fame but with an asterisk on their records.</statement>
     <statement id="6">The pressure to perform in MLB justifies the use of steroids.</statement>
     <statement id="7">A player&apos;s achievements should be judged by their performance, not whether they used steroids.</statement>
     <statement id="8">Players who used steroids were just trying to entertain the fans and should not be punished harshly.</statement>
     <statement id="9">MLB should have harsher penalties for steroid use to deter future players.</statement>
     <statement id="10">The league turned a blind eye to steroid use for years and should share the blame.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Steroid use in MLB should be accepted as part of the evolution of the game.</statement>
     <statement id="12">Players from the steroid era should not be judged differently than players from other eras.</statement>
     <statement id="13">Steroid use does not guarantee success in baseball.</statement>
     <statement id="14">MLB should focus on preventing future steroid use rather than punishing past users.</statement>
     <statement id="15">Using steroids is no different from using advanced training methods to enhance performance.</statement>
     <statement id="16">The steroid era made baseball more exciting and should not be viewed negatively.</statement>
     <statement id="17">Steroid testing in MLB is ineffective and easy to bypass.</statement>
     <statement id="18">Performance-enhancing drugs should be legalized and regulated in professional baseball.</statement>
     <statement id="19">Players should be responsible for their own bodies and allowed to take steroids if they choose.</statement>
     <statement id="20">The media exaggerated the impact of steroids on the game.</statement>
     <statement id="21">Steroids alone do not make someone a great baseball player.</statement>
     <statement id="22">The best players from the steroid era would have been great even without performance enhancers.</statement>
     <statement id="23">MLB should focus more on other forms of cheating, such as sign stealing, rather than steroids.</statement>
     <statement id="24">Younger players felt pressured to take steroids because MLB failed to enforce its own rules.</statement>
     <statement id="25">Steroid use in baseball is no worse than the use of painkillers and other legal substances.</statement>
     <statement id="26">The rise in home runs during the steroid era was good for baseball’s popularity.</statement>
     <statement id="27">Fans do not care whether players used steroids as long as the game is entertaining.</statement>
     <statement id="28">Punishing players for steroid use long after their careers are over is unfair.</statement>
     <statement id="29">Banning steroids has not stopped players from finding other ways to enhance performance.</statement>
     <statement id="30">MLB&apos;s drug policies are inconsistent and unfairly target certain players.</statement>
     <statement id="31">Steroid users helped MLB generate billions of dollars, yet they are the ones being punished.</statement>
     <statement id="32">Allowing steroid use would eliminate the secrecy and danger of underground doping.</statement>
     <statement id="33">MLB should focus on player safety rather than punishing past steroid users.</statement>
   </statements>